worthalike.com 2017-11-18

# WORTHaLIKE

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining the online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

**Collection of Personal Information**  
We have implemented Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising ([Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2799357?hl=en)). You can [opt-out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings. In addition, you can use the [Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) to disable tracking by Google Analytics. We will use the data provided by Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to develop the site and content around our user's interests. 

**Cookies**

**Google Analytics:**   
We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behaviour on our website. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our site and is not tied to personally identifiable information.We therefore do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are. We have turned on [Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2799357?hl=en) to get an idea of our demographics and user's interests. Please see above for how we use this data. 

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. 

**Contact**  
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Worthalike you may contact us: contact @ worthalike . com! 

**Links to Privacy Policy of 3rd-Party applications we use**
